{
    "subject": "resource/H._Robert_Horvitz",
    "predicate": "property/prizes",
    "object": "resource/Nobel_Prize_in_Physiology_or_Medicine",
    "human_readable": "H. Robert Horvitz has won the Nobel Prize in Physiology or Medicine.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9421693682670593,
            "question": "Name the scientist who won the Nobel Prize in Physiology or Medicine."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.927474319934845,
            "question": "Who won the Nobel Prize in Physiology or Medicine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8867658376693726,
            "question": "In what year did H. Robert Horvitz win the Nobel Prize?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8809615969657898,
            "question": "For what discovery did H. Robert Horvitz receive the Nobel Prize?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8145062327384949,
            "question": "What is the significance of winning a Nobel Prize in Physiology or Medicine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.65567547082901,
            "question": "What prestigious award did H. Robert Horvitz receive?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6266345977783203,
            "question": "Are there any other notable achievements associated with H. Robert Horvitz?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6054372787475586,
            "question": "What impact has H. Robert Horvitz's work had on the field of medicine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45626166462898254,
            "question": "What was H. Robert Horvitz's research focused on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4214736223220825,
            "question": "What field is H. Robert Horvitz known for?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=H. Robert Horvitz has won the Nobel Prize in Physiology or Medicine.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4131_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was H. Robert Horvitz's research focused on?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4131_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What impact has H. Robert Horvitz's work had on the field of medicine?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4131_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other notable achievements associated with H. Robert Horvitz?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4131_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4131_122.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4131_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4131_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4131_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4131_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4131_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4131_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4131_92.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4131_93.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4131_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple, as there are multiple mentions of H. Robert Horvitz winning the Nobel Prize in Physiology or Medicine in the year 2002."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about H. Robert Horvitz receiving the Nobel Prize in Physiology or Medicine in 2002 for his work on genetic regulation of organ development and programmed cell death, specifically through his studies of the roundworm Caenorhabditis elegans. This directly supports the statement that \"H. Robert Horvitz has won the Nobel Prize in Physiology or Medicine.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}